Anthony F. C. Wallace Papers 1920-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.64a
American Philosophical Society
- Series IX. Indian Claims, 15 linear feet (Box 172-199)
  - Fox Indians -- Sac and Fox Tribe of Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 83, 17, 1953
  - Fox Indians -- Sac and Fox Tribe of Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 83, 18, 1953
  - Fox Indians -- Sac and Fox Tribe of Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 83, 17, 1953
  - Fox Indians -- Sac and Fox Tribe of Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 158, 3, 1955
  - Fox Indians -- Sac and Fox Tribe of Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 158, 4, 1955
  - Fox Indians -- Sac and Fox Tribe of Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 158, 6, 1955
  - Fox Indians -- Sac and Fox Tribe of Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 158, 5, 1955
  - Fox Indians -- Sac and Fox Tribe of Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 83, 30, 1956
  - Fox Indians -- Sac and Fox Tribe of Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 83, 30, 1956
  - Fox Indians -- Sac and Fox Tribe of Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 83, 1, 1956
  - Fox Indians -- Sauk and Fox Chronology
  - Fox Indians -- Sauk and Fox Material #1
  - Fox Indians -- Sauk and Fox Material #2
  - Fox Indians -- Sauk and Fox Material #3
  - Fox Indians -- Sauk and Fox Treaties #1, 1815-1825
  - Fox Indians -- Sauk and Fox Treaties #2, 1829-1836
  - Fox Indians -- Sauk and Fox Treaties #3
  - Fox Indians -- Skinner, Alanson. Observation on the Ethnology of the Sauk Indians, 1923-1926
  - Fox Indians -- Treaty of 1804 and Surrounding Circumstances
  - Fox Indians -- Tribal Histories
  - Fox Indians -- United States Government Exhibits
  - Fox Indians -- Wallace, Anthony F.C. Iowa and Sac and Fox Indians in Iowa and Missouri #1
  - Fox Indians -- Wallace, Anthony F.C. Iowa and Sac and Fox Indians in Iowa and Missouri #2
  - Fox Indians -- Wallace, Anthony F.C. Iowa and Sac and Fox Indians in Iowa and Missouri #3
  - Fox Indians -- Wallace, Anthony F.C. Iowa and Sac and Fox Indians in Iowa and Missouri #4
  - Fox Indians -- Wallace, Anthony F.C. Iowa and Sac and Fox Indians in Iowa and Missouri #5
  - Fox Indians -- Wallace, Anthony F.C. Iowa and Sac and Fox Indians in Iowa and Missouri: Corrected copy #1
  - Fox Indians -- Wallace, Anthony F.C. Iowa and Sac and Fox Indians in Iowa and Missouri: Corrected copy #2
  - Fox Indians -- Whitney, Helen. Sauk and Fox Prisoners
  - Gue, Benjamin F., 1828-1904 -- History of Iowa from the Earliest Times to the Beginning of the Twentieth Century (excerpts)
  - Hodge, F.W. -- Handbook of American Indians North of Mexico (excerpts), 1909
  - Houck, Louis -- History of Missouri (extracts), 1909
  - Houck, Louis -- Spanish Regime in Missouri (excerpts)
  - Illinois Indians -- Correspondence and Finances
  - Illinois Indians -- Notes
  - Illinois Indians -- Wallace, Anthony F.C. Memorandum on Illinois Indians, 1956
  - Illinois State Historical Society -- Notes and Extracts
  - Illinois State Historical Society -- Notes and extracts
  - Illinois State Historical Society -- Notes, Extracts, Newsletters
  - Illinois State Historical Society -- Reprints
  - Indiana Historical Society -- Reprints
  - Indians of North America--Warfare -- Notes
  - Indians, Publication Catalogs
  - Iowa Indians -- Atwater, Caleb. Remarks Made on Tour to Prairie du Chien
  - Iowa Indians -- Black Hawk War, 1832 #1
  - Iowa Indians -- Black Hawk War, 1832 #2
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs #14
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs #6
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #1
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #10
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #11
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #12
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #13
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #15
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #2
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #3
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #4
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #5
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #7
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #8
  - Iowa Indians -- Bureau of Indian Affairs Records #9
  - Iowa Indians -- Chocteau, August. Indian Affairs, 1816
  - Iowa Indians -- Correspondence (Early)
  - Iowa Indians -- Finances
  - Iowa Indians -- Forsyth, Thomas. Account of the Manners and Customs of the Sauk and Fox Nations of Indians Tradition, 1827
  - Iowa Indians -- Forsyth, Thomas. Original Causes of the Troubles with a party of Sauk and Fox Indians under the direction or command of the Black Hawk who is no Chief., 1832
  - Iowa Indians -- Iowa Indians of Kansas and Nebraska: Trial Memorandum
  - Iowa Indians -- Iowa Indians: Miscellaneous Material
  - Iowa Indians -- Iowa Indians: Tribal Histories
  - Iowa Indians -- Jones, William. Ethnography of the Fox Indians (extracts), 1939
  - Iowa Indians -- Jones, William. Notes on the Fox Indians (extracts), 1911
  - Iowa Indians -- Marston, M. Letter to Dr. Morse, 1820
  - Iowa Indians -- Miscellaneous Material
  - Iowa Indians -- Newberry Library: Miscellaneous Material
  - Iowa Indians -- Peace Policy Period: 1804-1828
  - Iowa Indians -- Prehistoric and Historic Habitat of the Missouri and Oto Indians (extract)
  - Iowa Indians -- Removal from Suakenuk, 1828-1831 #1
  - Iowa Indians -- Removal from Suakenuk, 1828-1831 #2
  - Iowa Indians -- Reynolds, John. My Own Times: Embracing Also the History of My Life" (extracts), 1855
  - Iowa Indians -- Sauk and Fox Chronology
  - Iowa Indians -- Sauk and Fox Material #1
  - Iowa Indians -- Sauk and Fox Material #2
  - Iowa Indians -- Sauk and Fox Material #3
  - Iowa Indians -- Sauk and Fox Treaties #1, 1815-1825
  - Iowa Indians -- Sauk and Fox Treaties #2, 1829-1836
  - Iowa Indians -- Sauk and Fox Treaties #3
  - Iowa Indians -- Skinner, Alanson. Observation on the Ethnology of the Sauk Indians, 1923-1926
  - Iowa Indians -- Treaty of 1804 and Surrounding Circumstances
  - Iowa Indians -- Tribal Histories
  - Iowa Indians -- United States Government Exhibits
  - Iowa Indians -- Whitney, Helen. Sauk and Fox Prisoners
  - Iowa Journal of History and Politics -- Excerpts
  - Iroquois Indians -- Barnholt, William I.--Cuyahoga-Tuscarawas Portage: A Documentary History, 1954
  - Iroquois Indians -- Beauchamp, William--History of New York Iroquois (notes), 1905
  - Iroquois Indians -- Big Tree and Sale of Reservations: Miscellaneous Manuscripts
  - Iroquois Indians -- Brunhouse, Robert (notes), 2 items
  - Iroquois Indians -- Bureau of American Ethnology, Smithsonian: Articles on English policy and New York policy
  - Iroquois Indians -- Cammerhoff, Br. and David Zeisberger: Diary of the Joruney of Br. Cammerhoff and David Zeisberger to the Five Nations from May 3-14 to August 6-17, 1750
  - Iroquois Indians -- Deardorff, Merle H.:Cornplanter Grant in Warren County
  - Iroquois Indians -- Hays, John: Journal, 1760
  - Iroquois Indians -- History of New York Iroquois (notes), 1905
  - Iroquois Indians -- Holland Land Company: Notes
  - Iroquois Indians -- Indian Records Vol. I, 1668-1838 (Works Progress Administration), page 201 to end
  - Iroquois Indians -- Indian Records Vol. I, 1668-1838 (Works Progress Administration), to page 200
  - Iroquois Indians -- Indian Records Vol. II, 1839-1859 (Works Progress Administration), page 201 to end
  - Iroquois Indians -- Indian Records Vol. II, 1839-1859 (Works Progress Administration), to page 200
  - Iroquois Indians -- Indian Records Vol. III, 1860-1883 (Works Progress Administration)
  - Iroquois Indians -- Journals of the Continental Congress, 1774-1789 (notes)
  - Iroquois Indians -- Kent, Donald H.: Historical Report on the Niagara River and the Niagara River Strip to 1759, 1974
  - Iroquois Indians -- Kirkland, Samuel
  - Iroquois Indians -- Lindley, Jacob: His Account of His "Religious Visit" to the Friends in Canada, and to Indians on Buffalo Creek, in 1797
  - Iroquois Indians -- Maclay, Samuel: Journal, 1790 (notes)
  - Iroquois Indians -- Mohr, Walter: Federal Indian Relations 1774-1788 (notes)
  - Iroquois Indians -- Morse, Jedediah: Report to the Secretary of War of the United States on Indian Affairs, 1822 (excerpts)
  - Iroquois Indians -- Navarre, 1742: Report
  - Iroquois Indians -- O'Reilly Papers, New York Historical Society and Pickering Papers, Massachusetts Historical Society (notes)
  - Iroquois Indians -- Pennsylvania Archives (notes)
  - Iroquois Indians -- Pickering Papers (Massachusetts Historical Society): American Ethnology (notes)
  - Iroquois Indians -- Post, Christian Frederick: Journal, 1760
  - Iroquois Indians -- Savery, William: Journal of Life, Travels, and Religious Labours of William Savery
  - Iroquois Indians -- Seaver, James Everett: Life of Mary Jemison (notes)
  - Iroquois Indians -- Semple, Ellen Churchill: American History and its Geographic Conditions (extracts)
  - Iroquois Indians -- Seneca Nation of Indians and Tonawanda Band of Seneca Indians, vs. the United States
  - Iroquois Indians -- Seneca Nation of Indians vs. United States of America and Tonawanda Band of Seneca Indians vs. the United States of America, Dockets No. 342-A and 368-A
  - Iroquois Indians -- Seneca Nation of Indians vs. United States of America and Tonawanda Band of Seneca Indians vs. the United States of America, Dockets No. 342-H, Appeal 11-63, 1965; 1 item
  - Iroquois Indians -- Seneca-Cayuga Tribe of Oklahoma vs. the United States of America, Docket 341, Trial Memorandum
  - Iroquois Indians -- Sipe, C. Hale. Principal Indian Towns of Western Pennsylvania
  - Iroquois Indians -- Six Nations et. al. vs. the United States of America, Appeal No. 8-63
  - Iroquois Indians -- Six Nations Northwest Pennsylvania and the Erie Triangle vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 344: Trial Memorandum
  - Iroquois Indians -- Six Nations, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 89: Ohio Trial Memoranda
  - Iroquois Indians -- Six Nations, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 344: Final Order
  - Iroquois Indians -- Six Nations, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket Nos. 342-A and 344: Correspondence (New York and Pennsylvania)
  - Iroquois Indians -- Six Nations, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 89: Ohio Trial Memoranda
  - Iroquois Indians -- Six Nations, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 344: Final Order, 1963
  - Iroquois Indians -- Six Nations: Notes
  - Iroquois Indians -- Snyderman, George S. Concepts of Land Ownership Among the Iroquois and their Neighbors
  - Iroquois Indians -- Snyderman, George S. Notes on the Economic Life of the Indians of the Northwest Territory and Ohio
  - Iroquois Indians -- Testimony #1
  - Iroquois Indians -- Treaties and Treaty Journals 1701-1857
  - Iroquois Indians -- United States House of Representatives: Compilation of Materials Relating to the Indians of the United States, etc. by Subcommittee on Indian Affairs, 1950
  - Iroquois Indians -- Washington, George: Journal of a Tour to the Ohio River in 1770
  - Iroquois Indians -- Washington, George: Writings (notes), 1784-1793
  - Iroquois Indians -- Wilkinson, Norman: Robert Morris and the Treaty of Big Tree
  - Kane, Michal -- American Indian Ethnohistoric Conference Newsletter No. 1, 1956
  - Kane, Michal -- Chippewa Notes
  - Kane, Michal -- Dakota (Eastern Dakota): Notes
  - Kane, Michal -- Exhibits for Dr. Wallace from National Archives, 2 items
  - Kane, Michal -- Finances
  - Kane, Michal -- Illinois Indians: Notes and Research Results
  - Kane, Michal -- Iowa
  - Kane, Michal -- Miami Indians: Notes and Research Results
  - Kane, Michal -- Notes Index: Johnson Papers, Documents Relating to the Colonial History of New York, and Documentary History of the State of New York
  - Kane, Michal -- Ottawa Indians
  - Kane, Michal -- Pickering Papers (notes)
  - Kane, Michal -- Potawatomi Locations: Notes
  - Kane, Michal -- Potawatomi Political Organization
  - Kane, Michal -- Potawatomi Treaty Signers
  - Kane, Michal -- Safi-Sioux Conflict: Notes and Explanation for Map
  - Kane, Michal -- Sioux Claims: Calendar of Selections from Senate and House Documents
  - Kane, Michal -- Sioux's Eye View of Minnesota History
  - Kane, Michal -- Treaties of 1833 and 1846
  - Kane, Michal -- Treaty of 1804; Sac and Fox
  - Kane, Michal -- War Among the Sac and Fox; the Black Hawk "War;" Sac and Fox Locations and Tribal Movements
  - Kane, Michal -- Wea and Piankeshaw Locations and Fur Trade in Cession 151: Bibliographic Survey
  - Kane, Michal -- Wea Notes
  - Kaw Indians -- Kaw Tribe, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket Nos. 33, 34, and 35: Trial Memorandum, 1951
  - Kellogg, Louise Phelps, d. 1942 -- Early Narratives of the Northwest: 1634-1699 (excerpt)
  - Kickapoo Indians -- Kickapoo Tribe of Kansas, the Kickapoo Tribe of Oklahoma, the Kickapoo Nation, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 194 and Trial Memorandum, 1951
  - Kickapoo Indians -- Kickapoo Tribe of Kansas, the Kickapoo Tribe of Oklahoma, the Kickapoo Nation, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Dockets 315 and 317, 1951
  - Kickapoo Indians -- Notes
  - Kickapoo Indians -- Tribal Histories
  - Kinnaird, Lawrence -- Spain in the Mississippi Valley (excerpts)
  - Le Raye, Charles -- Topographical Description of the State of Ohio Indiana Territory, and Louisiana
  - Lea, Albert Miller, 1807-1890 -- Notes on the Wisconsin Territory; Particularly with Reference to the Iowa District, or the Black Hawk Purchase, 1836
  - Marest, Gabriel, 1662-1714 -- Letter in Neill, N.D., History of Minnesota (extract), 1700; 2 items
  - Margry, Pierre, 1818-1894 -- Narratives and Inedited Memoirs for the History of France, 1867
  - McCoy, Isaac, 1784-1846 -- History of Baptist Indian Missions (excerpts), 1822
  - McKenney, Thomas Loraine, 1785-1859 -- Young Mahaskah (excerpt from History of the Indian Tribes of North America)
  - Miami Indians -- Miami Tribe of Oklahoma, also known as the Miami Tribe, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 67, 1951
  - Miami Indians -- Miami Tribe of Oklahoma, also known as the Miami Tribe, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 67 (Trial Memoranda), 1951
  - Miami Indians -- Miami Tribe of Oklahoma, also known as the Miami Tribe, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket Nos. 251-256, 1951
  - Miami Indians -- Miami Tribe of Oklahoma: Tribal Histories
  - Miami Indians -- Miami Tribe vs. the United States of America: Treaties, 1951
  - Miami Indians -- Miscellaneous Material
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Historical Societies: Chicago
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Historical Societies: Indiana
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Historical Societies: Iowa
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Historical Societies: Kansas
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Historical Societies: Massachusetts
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Historical Societies: Michigan
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Historical Societies: Minnesota
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Historical Societies: Missouri
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Historical Societies: Pennsylvania
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Historical Societies: Presbyterian
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Hutchins, Thomas: Papers
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Johnson, Sir William: Papers
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Journals of the Continental Congress
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Minutes of Provincial Council of Pennsylvania
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Miscellaneous
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- National Archives: Martin, John L., compiler, List of Documents Concerning the Negotiation of Ratified Indian Treaties 1801-1869
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- O'Callaghan, E.B., ed. Documents Relating to the Colonial History of New York
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- O'Reilly, Henry: Papers (New York Historical Society)
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Pennsylvania Archives
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Pickering, Timothy: Papers (Massachusetts Historical Society)
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Thwaites, Reuben Gold and Samuel Kellogg (Wisconsin Historical Society, Draper Collection)
  - Miscellaneous Manuscript Collections -- Washington, George: Papers
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Breaking up of Tribal Organization
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Greenville Treaty
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- High Cost of Killing Indians
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Indian Land Policy in the Mexican Cession
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Indian Removal Policy
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Miscellaneous Material #1
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Miscellaneous Material #2
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Moravian Archives (in Deutsch)
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Notes
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Notes
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Otoe and Missouri, et.al vs. the United States of America, Docket Nos. 11-!, 138, and 332-A, 1959
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Peoria Tribe of Oklahoma and Mabel Staton Parker on behalf of the Piankeshaw Nation and the Absentee Delaware Tribe of Oklahoma and the Delaware Nationvs. the United States of America, Docket 289, 1951
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Peoria Tribe of Oklahoma and Mabel Staton Parker on behalf of the Piankeshaw Nation vs. the United States of America, Docket 99, 1951
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Peoria Tribe of Oklahoma, Guy Froman on behalf of the Peoria Nation, and Fred Ensworth on behalf of the Kaskaskia Nation vs. the United States of America, Docket Nos. 313 and 314 and Trial Memorandum
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Pressure to Force Indian Land Cessions
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Trespass on Indian Lands
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Wallace, Anthony F.C. American Indian Land Tenure and Political Organization in the Northeastern Agricultural Area, 1650-1830, 1955
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Wallace, Anthony F.C. Bibliography
  - Miscellaneous Tribes -- Wallace, Anthony F.C. Policy Toward the Northeastern Indian Tribes, 1783-1795
  - Missouri Historical Review -- Excerpts
  - Missouri Indians -- Otoe and Missouri Tribes of Indians vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 11, 1950
  - Missouri Indians -- Otoe and Missouria Tribe of Indians vs. the United States, Docket No. 11-A: Objections and Reply
  - Missouri Indians -- Tribal Histories
  - Morse, Jedidiah, 1761-1826 -- American Gazetteer. Report to the Secretary of War of the United States on Indian Affairs, Comprising a Narrative of a Tour (excerpts), 1822
  - Moses, John -- Illinois, Historical and Statistical Comprising the Essential Facts (extracts)
  - Muckleshoot Indians -- Muckleshoot Tribe vs. the United States, Docket No. 98
  - Nasatir, Abraham Phineas, 1904- -- Before Lewis and Clark: documents illustrating the history of the Missouri, 1785-1804 (excerpts)
  - Ohio Research -- Correspondence
  - Ohio Research -- Finances
  - Ohio Research -- Notes, 2 items
  - Oneida Indians -- Oneida Nation of New York, et.al. vs. the United States of America, Docket 301, 1951
  - Oneida Indians -- Oneida of Wisconsin: Correspondence
  - Oneida Indians -- Oneida of Wisconsin: Finances
  - Oto Indians -- Otoe and Missouri Tribes of Indians vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 11, 1950
  - Oto Indians -- Otoe and Missouria Tribe of Indians vs. the United States, Docket No. 11-A: Objections and Reply
  - Oto Indians -- Tribal Histories
  - Ottawa Indians -- Notes
  - Ottawa Indians -- Ohio Trial Memorandum
  - Ottawa Indians -- Ottawa of Oklahoma: Tribal History
  - Ottawa Indians -- Ottawa Tribe of Indians vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 40-B, 133, 1952
  - Ottawa Indians -- Ottawa Tribe, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 133, 1951
  - Parsons, William -- Bibliography and Notes
  - Pawnee Indians -- Pawnee Indian Tribe of Oklahoma vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 10: Findings
  - Pawnee Indians -- Pawnee Indian Tribe of Oklahoma vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 10: Opinion
  - Peckham, Howard Henry, 1910- -- Pontiac and the Indian Uprising (excerpt), 1947
  - Pennsylvania Archaeologist -- Excerpts
  - Peoria Indians -- Peoria Tribe of Oklahoma and Fred Ensworth on behalf of the Kaskaskia Nation, Docket No. 66
  - Peoria Indians -- Peoria Tribe of Oklahoma: Tribal Histories, 1949
  - Perrot, Nicolas, 1644 1718 -- Memoir on the Mores, Customs, and Religion of the Savages of North America, 1864
  - Piankeshaw Indians -- Notes
  - Pike, Zebulon Montgomery, 1779-1813 -- Account of Expeditions to Sources of the Mississippi, 1807
  - Population -- Notes
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Finances
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Hannahville Indian Community, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Miscellaneous Docket Nos.: Memoranda, 1951
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Notes #1
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Notes #2, 12 items
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Potawatomi Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 71, 1950
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Potawatomi Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 71-A and Petitioners' Brief
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Potawatomi Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 128, 1951
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Potawatomi Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 146, 1951
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Potawatomi Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 216, 1951
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Potawatomi Indians of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket Nos. 306 and 311, 1951
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Potawatomi Indians vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 146 and Trial Memoranda
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Potawatomi Indians, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket Nos. 146 and 15-M: Petitioners' Findings and Brief (consolidated for hearing with miscellaneous other docket nos.)
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Potawatomi Indians vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 217: Trial Memorandum, 1953
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Quimby, George. Potawatomi Indians
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Regulations Book #1: Tribal History (Preliminary Report)
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Regulations Book #2: Treaties #1
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Regulations Book #3: Treaties #2
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Strong, James, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 13-M, et. al. (includes AFC Wallace testimony), 1956
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Transcript of Hearing, 7 July 1953 (includes AFC Wallace testimony)
  - Potawatomi Indians -- Wallace, Anthony F.C. Potawatomi Political System and Tribal Membership, 1953
  - Propositions
  - Receipts
  - Reynolds, John, 1788-1865 -- Pioneer History of Illinois Containing the Discovery in 1673, and the History of the Country to the Year 1818?(extracts), 1852
  - Salter, William, 1821-1910 -- Iowa, the First Free State in the Louisiana Purchase, 1905
  - Schoolcraft, Henry Rowe, 1793-1864 -- Archives of Aboriginal Knowledge (excerpts), 1860
  - Shawnee Indians -- Eastern Shawnee Tribe of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket No. 335, 1951
  - Shawnee Indians -- Eastern Shawnee Tribe of Oklahoma, et. al. vs. the United States of America, Docket 335: Ohio Trial Memoranda, 1953
  - Shawnee Indians -- Notes
  - Shawnee Indians -- Tribal Histories